kunena.org 2014-02-09

# Kunena - To Speak! Next Generation Forum Component for Joomla - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

Details
     Last Updated on Thursday, 28 November 2013 10:26 
     Published on Friday, 20 July 2012 17:19 

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or contact us for questions about problems that you may be having with the software products obtained from this website. When registering on our site you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, gender and geograhical location. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### What do we use your information for?

Information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs;
  * To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs;
  * To process transactions
  * To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to enquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [Terms of use](http://www.kunena.org/terms-of-use).

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
